Your skin is your largest organ and it will absorb any chemicals we put on it.
So why not make your own all natural cleanser?
I'm Jackie with how to make herbal skin cleansing cream.
You'll save time and money and have fun in the process.
Crush one once of herb leaves or one once of flowers in a cup of water.
Pour the mixture into a pot and add another cup of water to cover it.
Bring it to a boil slowly, especially if you're using flowers.
Simmer for about three minutes, cool it, and then strain the leaves and flowers.
Refrigerate the mixture for about two hours.
Melt one ounce of lanolin or bee's wax in a double boiler and stir in three to four ounces of almond oil or avocado oil very slowly.
Remove it from the heat and mix in one ounce of the herb or flower water from the fridge using a whisk.
Apply it to your face avoiding the eyes and lips and wash off with water.
Remember, making your own skin cleanser gives you all natural ingredients for a radiant glow.
I'm Jackie with how to make herbal skin cleansing cream.
Have a beautiful day.